hello my name is green and welcome back
to another episode of hermitcraft and
i'm not on renbob's toilet
for the reason that you think i am
basically we made a brand new secret
entrance to our secret tunnel instead of
having the hole that was just sitting in
my rv
we made it so if you flush this toilet
it goes down
and you end up in the secret tunnel but
unfortunately we've had a bit of an
issue
yeah look at this
look at this
i thought when i was building this i was
fighting the grass left right and center
but
look it somehow crept in without any of
us noticing
and the whole thing's just covered in
grass now it's actually really annoying
because this is basically
having to re do it redo the whole thing
i'd have to redo the whole thing take
out each and every one of these grass
blocks
place in a dirt block and then i
guarantee you it will end up exactly as
it is now so i'm now debating whether
it's worth the time trying to fight this
grass block shenanigans or just go with
it just let it grow
i i'm not even sure but i was
a little bit like oh no when i saw this
either way i need to set up something
here i actually need a couple of armor
stands and i'm no good with armor stands
what i'm going to do is ask zombie clio
who is an expert
in the armor stand world and ask her to
make them for me which means giving her
a little bit of an instruction so i'm
going to go and drop this off which
tells her exactly what i need and to pay
her some diamonds for it so we're going
to quickly head over to cleo's base to
give her the instructions
so that she can help us out on this
because it is a little bit tricky for me
to use armor stands i've not really
visited cleo's base before but this is a
very good example of
three greens around a map look at this
she's so good with the armor stance
hello
where have you been there's so many like
armistance how has she done all this
anyway this is exactly what we need but
i don't really know where she keeps all
of her
storage and stuff ah there we go
i thought i'd find her storage right as
long as i put the book in here
then she will definitely come across it
if these instructions don't confuse cleo
i don't know what will so it says top
secret hi cleo i need an off the books
armor stand creation can you flush
yourself down red bob's toilet in hippie
land signs there will tell you where to
go and what to do payment is included
here for your troubles so we're done put
that in here and i'll pay 20 diamonds i
don't know if that's enough but i think
it's a good start she could always ask
for more if she needs to so those
instructions and maybe i should leave a
sign here as well
top secret assignment there we go
mission accomplished
and it will make a lot of sense what
that was all about
a little bit later on but trust me it's
really really important since we're here
in the shopping district you might
remember from a few episodes ago that i
created the now extension to sahara and
i didn't really fully understand it all
but actually iskall has just completed
all of the redstone for it and i think
that's that's him there and he's asked
us to get in a meeting so that we can
sort out some of the finer details of
this project and then hopefully we can
get a few hermits to buy a subscription
to it
so that they can pay us to spend more
that's right we're gonna make a lot of
diamonds from this hopefully so let's go
and hop into the meeting room where
we're going to wait for iskaw and mumbo
well
i hope mumbo turns up because we all
remember what you did last time
i don't want to have to take your
mustache again although he's got it back
at least so
maybe we can get rid of this let's just
hope that he turns up okay well well
well
look who decided to show up
you're right finally
i've missed one meeting
it's it's only one i can't help but i
can't even notice that you've also
removed my chair as well like i can't
believe how cut throat you guys are
don't turn up to meetings we've actually
added your your uh chair to us and now
mine's a bigger chair that's that's how
this works um that is both have we both
have functions in our chairs it's gail
do you wanna give him his new chair
yeah yeah i'm appreciating the recline
the front panel
my feet don't even fit on this thing
until you start turning up to meetings
this is your chair
you've missed just as many meetings with
me
i can't hear you let me get down to your
level
all right
oh this is ridiculous
you know what hang on
look okay i'm taking my chair
and i'm gonna make my way
you know what i'm not cut there we go
there we go there we go all right okay
continue continue the meeting
we're here to discuss the next stage of
sahara's evolution which is saharan now
which is a brilliant scheme where we get
hermits to pay us to buy more stuff from
us
it's it's pure profit and that does
sound it's a win-win it's a win-win-win
it's a win-win
yeah i have been a bit busy being a
hippie recently so yeah why what is that
stuff you're wearing and and what's
consider showering and soap
yeah i'm above i'm above him like this
is awful
i smell flowery is that sandals yeah is
that sandals or is that rendog's beard
on your feet
yeah they're they're actually they're
they're beard hair sandals it's a
combination of the pair all right you
can ignore my my hippie attire we're in
business sahara mode okay iska please
explain
what sahara now is and how it works
yes
okay so sahara now is a an exclusive
membership that requires you to have a
membership coin boop that you purchase
for a price that we need to decide and
when you've purchased it you get access
to the lounge area which i've i i have
renovated slightly since you guys last
saw it and
should we fly over there yeah let's go
yeah yeah let's let's actually take a
look so so as you can see i've renovated
i've taken the liberty to renovate the
lounge to include this sahara now
function and with a membership token
other hermits are allowed up to this
area i've also made like an entrance for
it but i can show you that later
when you are a member you get to access
all the different offers that we present
and that is this little mechanic here
i've also written a book with
instructions and it's kind of like a
good test for me to see if you guys
understand it by reading the book i was
elected to lead not to read yeah i was
going to say you want you want us to
read all right
all of the books
where are the signs where are the signs
signs signs are messy
this is an exclusive thing no one looks
human
every hermit i've ever seen just goes oh
there's a book right what does this
button do
well now you purchased an offer and now
you get presented with the next offer oh
i purchased it oh man this deal sucked
well you didn't have to buy it you have
to buy it well i didn't i didn't know
what the button did because no one put a
sign there
yeah
i'm not going to put signs here boys
i'm not going to put science all right
purchase deal was that that hard
was that difficult this gal's always
wanted to be a published author um and
we'll give him we'll give him this one
boom
i assume this cycle's through and that's
the purchase button boom cycle the next
offer purchased it was that hard that
wasn't difficult at all
fine
very fine to be fair that does actually
look and i just saved four pages of book
you know these these deals are pretty
good they're all 10 diamonds though
maybe i think some of them could be a
little cheaper but
how much are we going to charge for the
membership that's the next question
because these are only good in relation
to that like that is a lot of sea
lanterns for 10 diamonds plus the
shulker box
wait hang hang on
uh so about the stack of stephens that
is missing from that box
did you take some
i
played myself for this i've
i just saw a box of them in the meeting
room and i was like well i do need some
sea lanterns
i took one of the
this is why this is why you have a
button for a chair
yeah
that is so funny this is why our chairs
are bigger than yours put it back
okay so
how many times does a membership cost
well it's going to be lifetime right
it's going to be a lifetime membership
yeah so
ah
15 12 diamonds
okay it's too cheap they get the show
that's why he's sitting on a button and
win yeah yeah all right
a thousand diamonds
that's too far in the other one
direction
okay
that escalated quickly that is a hundred
diamonds
uh hundred diamonds hundreds are really
nice figure because it's it's a quite a
large price tag but when they actually
oh are they allowed to come and see the
deals how do they know
they don't we have to do we have to we
have to sell it to them through
marketing
oh
okay so 100 diamonds they don't know
what they're getting until they pay 100
diamonds then they see the deals but the
deals are ridiculously good
so hopefully word of mouth
helps we just need one person to sign up
but should all shulker boxes be ten
diamonds or should we differ i think
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah that sounds like a
good move so we need some dirt cheap
shulker boxes that are filled with
really good stuff that people will then
yeah you know they'll tweet about it
stuff like that
guys yeah for example no maybe not all
right i mean yes i propose a little
competition between the three of us then
to see how many memberships we can sell
to the other hermits and that means
we've all got to take on a little bit of
a marketing uh program scheme
by ourselves to see how many we can get
all right so if i if i sell three
memberships i bring in 300 diamonds
iskall maybe only got one sale and maybe
mumbo got 10. mumbo wins yep what do you
think that is the likely results of this
competition as well by the way well
that's more than around the surface
i'm going to invite some people
and just start bringing people in
thanks dude so there's a little
competition to see who can sell the most
memberships and also is it okay if i add
some deal boxes of my own as well yeah
that's the whole idea both of you should
add deal boxes because awesome
yeah yeah that that's that's the whole
point whole point do you want to see how
members access this place oh yeah yeah
absolutely no one can even know that bit
i'm guessing anyways i put this in here
let me i mean i've not seen this because
yeah yeah press the button
i like the beats
how do i get it back
well
you should open the shulker box before
you go it's like a keycard insert
so
where's the sign that says that
look all right
it's just assumed that you would pick it
back up okay it's just assumed you're
that person at the supermarket that
leaves the pound in the trolley isn't it
you're that person
i don't know you know it's not it's not
clear instructions not clear got my
hands stuck in the machine
there you go i've lost my key card can i
have another one please that'll be
another hundred diamonds okay so we
all right okay you're gonna actually
[Laughter]
wait
take key card out before entering
wow that doesn't look cool style at all
i love it
take key card out
i did it
nice i messed it up
instructions at the top weren't clear
fell
down all right
[Laughter]
i wonder
i spend more
more time green proofing and green and
stuff oh yeah don't even go there about
that sort of thing
it's a nightmare
just saying everyone that's shopped at
sahara so far has been super confused
okay
so wait so let me just to summarize the
meeting okay because clearly i'm the
only sensible one here so
um uh so i i now have the tallest chair
by default because i'm on top of green's
chair so we've sorted that we've
resolved that problem that we were
having that was a serious problem that
was number one on the schedule uh number
two is that sahara now is quite good
we've wiped out the price which is a
hundred diamonds uh we're going to be
doing marketing campaigns and green
isn't allowed access to any of this
stuff anymore because
he's useless what
i'm just trying to make sure the
customer has the don't stand next to me
i didn't agree to that i've got the
biggest i stand next to you he stinks as
well he sleeps as well if there's any
conclusion from this is that a hippie
has made it into sahara yeah and it it
now is it's now very foul it's very
stupid if i could roll my eyes in
minecraft i would
right so we're in we're on a competition
to sell the most memberships through our
marketing campaigns uh gentlemen's rules
okay gentleman's rules no no back
dealings you can't you can't go and
offer
uh discounts for the hundred diamonds
it's got to be 100 diamonds you can't
pay them back once you've got a
gentleman's rules you've got to be
honest with it and the best
marketing and adverts will win right
deadlines
none just going to leave it endless
all right until i have the most i think
that'll do okay you can hear them
all right sweet sounds good to me
so so wait guys is the horror now opened
is it open oh no we forgot to open it
hang on
we're really bad
fly back over to you i'm prepared i've
prepared um not quite
as big an opening as our original one
but i've got an opening rocket here for
sahara now budgets are tight because
sahara has been not making enough money
right you ready um yes count down with
me three
two two
one one yay sahara now's open
[Applause]
it wasn't even yellow well that was
actually a pretty awesome meeting but we
need to get back to being a hippie
because i mean that's the skin i'm
wearing at the moment and the next thing
that i want to work on is this this
hippie silo that everyone's been
wondering what it's about i've actually
made this giant cube and this is what
i'm going to be making in here the big
distraction for area 77 this is going to
be one of the funnest pranks of the
season you heard me pranks this is going
to be awesome but it's actually
something that's going to take a few
weeks to do and i've prepared a bunch of
blocks as i usually have to do this is
the stuff you don't see we have to
collect all this in the background to
make projects like that possible so what
we're going to do is a quick time lapse
of building this and uh by the end of it
you'll know exactly what it is
so let's begin
so in this little time lapse i say
little it took two hours it's not little
at all and then gathering all the
resources took many hours so when i say
little i don't mean little at all but it
will take only half a minute
what we're going to be making actually
i'm not going to tell you what we're
making because i think you can work out
what it is but scaling up said thing
that i am now building is not easy it's
not easy at all the thing that i am
building has been made three times
already in this hippie commune it is
something that works a lot better when
it's smaller i think i've done a pretty
good job of imitating it about three
times the size
however
it took so long i was like oh when i was
building it anyway that is the full
thing and yeah i'm pretty sure i could
put a few more details in this however i
think you get the point and that's the
main thing
if you can't tell what it is i i don't
know i don't i don't know how to help
you
well there you have it two hours later
and we've got ourselves a giant rv in a
silo
this is only part one
of my three-part plan okay and i'm
guessing that you will
guess
what's going to happen to this rv
but i'm not gonna give anything away
just yet
because i'm guessing you'll know what's
going to happen to this but maybe not
what comes after that so i've obviously
built this giant rv it's got nothing on
the inside at the moment but that will
change at some point and basically
if you have guest already this is going
to launch in the air
what it's going to do after that i'm not
going to say
however
i need area 77
to know that it's going to launch
because obviously they can take a look
at this and make their guesses
but really this distraction isn't quite
enough
and what i really need
is a countdown clock
something visible with a big five four
three however many days it is until
launch to show them that it's gonna go
up and then when it actually does launch
i want it to count down five four three
two one
now my redstone ability
well
it's not great as we all know
so
i would like to do something that we
haven't done which is recruit an extra
hippie to the group
at least recruit a hippie that's going
to help us do a bit of a redstone
project
and i do have someone in mind
but i'm going to open it up to the group
and i'm going to put an advert out there
to apply to join the hippies so that
they can do
exactly what i said the big launch
countdown
so actually i'm gonna have to i'm gonna
have to head back to the shopping
district again
man this journey
it does take a while so i'm in the
shopping district outside of i trade
this is a pretty um used nether portal
here so what i'm gonna do is put a
advert right here for who we're looking
for so we'll put wanted
wanted redstone based hippie to help
fight the man to apply please contact
green and renbob for an interview that
way we can make sure we're getting the
right person for the job
and now i've got to go all the way back
this journey
i must admit i've made this journey
about a million times
and
it is pretty dull
especially when this happens
what no
actually while we're here on our way
back have we made oh
yes please we've got 30 diamonds
looks like some people
hit the lava wow people have been busy
playing this game i've got a restock at
some point but there's still a few left
open if people want to play i'm going to
add those 30 diamonds to my chest
excellent stuff and if you're wondering
about my
lava mini game the floor is lava mini
game
well i'll be completely honest with you
this doesn't happen very often but i i
have done a little bit of work in here
and i am still continuing to work on it
you can see our hippie paintings there
love um i've actually lost heart in this
project i think
i think
i don't know what happened but
it just suddenly
became very
painful to keep building this i will
finish this uh but i don't want you guys
to think that i'm making loads and loads
of progress on this each and every
episode because i'm i'm simply not so
what i'm going to do is i'm going to be
honest with you and i am going to just
close it up not not indefinitely i'm
just gonna put this on hold until i can
sort out all the stuff in hippie land
which i'm finding much more entertaining
at the moment so
uh
i'll tell you what i'm just gonna put
opening
soon
there we go that that that's that's what
people do when when they put something
on hold isn't it right so i don't know
how long it is gonna take me but i will
come back to this a little later but
it's such an awesome build and it is
gonna be such an awesome game that i
will have to finish it a little bit
later on but to get back to the hippie
world or hippie land or whatever we're
calling this this commune
there's a lot to do
but i'm afraid that that will have to
wait
until next episode we got a lot done
today and next episode i'm hoping to do
uh some sales i need to make some sales
for my sahara membership i want to make
as many diamonds as possible for sahara
because it's not been particularly
profitable at the moment we still need
to break even but this membership thing
could be really really cool
so
we got our rv built we had a big meeting
and we're preparing for um sahara
membership all right thank you very much
for watching and i'll see you in the
next episode in which we're gonna do
some really cool things see you later
goodbye